Abram Shook - Austin, Texas | 617-686-4263 | shookstack.atx@gmail.com

LinkedIn | Gitlab | Spotify | Record Label

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Over 20 years of experience in multiple industries including tech, hospitality, training and music, with an eagerness to learn new skill sets and a focus on continuous improvement. Pursuing a career in software engineering at the intersection of creativity and programming. Adaptable problem solver with a calm, purposeful work ethic.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

DEVELOPER: JavaScript - React - TypeScript - Next.js - AWS - Node.js - Ruby - Rails - AWS - HTML - CSS - Docker - Git

AUDIO PRODUCTION: Logic - ProTools - Ableton

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

About Me - Website

Simple portfolio build using HTML5 and JavaScript with demos and links for both composition/music related projects as well as my software development builds.

Boaters List - Website

Niche search engine and community platform connecting water enthusiasts with marine related services across the globe.

The Song Sifter - Github | Demo

Musical idea generator for writing and arrangement.

EXPERIENCE

Boater's List Remote
Lead Developer 3/2023 - present

- Continuous coding for UI/UX, bug fixes, dependency upgrades, and site maintenance
- Setup the companies first detailed analytics tracking for more granular statics on user interactions
- Performed AWS audit to pinpoint budget bloat and drastically cut overhead within first 2 weeks of joining project
- Grew the tech team, adding and onboarding two new devs, within the first 3 months of my hire date

Shook Sounds Production House

Austin, TX

Owner/Operator

09/2005 - present

- Produced numerous syncs based on client briefs for both Static West and Frog Music licensing
- Composed library tracks for Moving Illusion; an LA based film/tv/ad placement company
- Hired as a touring and studio musician for Heartless Bastards, Shearwater, The Low Lows among others
- Signed artist with Western Vinyl Records with 6 albums released and multiple collaborative projects

Pushqiq/ATXOnstage

Remote

Software Engineer

8/2022 - 3/2023

Data aggregation and management for music-related sites using Node.js and Typescript

Accenture Remote

SME 11/2020 - 04/2022

• Pinpointed areas of improvement and implemented new guidelines to adhere to metrics and compliance regulations

Hai Hospitality

Austin, TX

Trainer/Opening Captain

02/2006 -10/2018

Lead a team of 40+ employees through trainings and standards of service with one-on-one reviews and mentorship

EDUCATION

AWS Cloud Practitioner

Austin, TX

Completed Amazon's certification program for AWS cloud fundamentals

02/2023

Flatiron School

Austin, TX 04/2022 - 08/2022

Full Stack Web Development, Ruby on Rails and JavaScript program

Cabrillo College

music performance

Santa Cruz, CA